Maxwell Hankner

Software Engineer

2488 Waiomao Rd. Honolulu, HI 96816

612-978-5994
maxwellhankner@gmail.com
maxwellhankner.com
github.com/maxwellhankner
linkedin.com/in/maxwell-hankner

Summary

Software engineer with at least one year of experience in various web technologies. Searching for a position where I can put my existing skillset to use and further my knowledge in the industry. Committed to leveraging resources, creativity, and problem-solving skills to overcome challenging obstacles and create better business solutions.

Technical Skills

HTML, CSS, Javascript, Bootstrap, Styled Components, React, Redux, Redux-Saga, Node.js, Mongo, Three.js, Github, Photoshop, AdobeXD

Education

University of Minnesota / Full-Stack Web Dev Bootcamp

March 2020 - June 2020, St. Paul, MN

Montana State University / Bachelor of Computer Science

Fall 2016 - Spring 2017, Bozeman, MT

Saint John's University / Bachelor of Computer Science

Fall 2015 - Spring 2016, St. Joseph, MN

Work Experience

Web Developer / Self Employed

April 2020 - Current, Honolulu, HI

I have always been interested in web development and, more recently, been able to get started on a career in the industry. Since graduating from my bootcamp, I have done work for two clients. One of the clients is an insurance adjustment company and the other is an online clothing store.

Smooth Moves, LLC / Owner

February 2017 - November 2019, Minneapolis, MN

Smooth Moves was a furniture moving company I started. At its peak, there were 17 employees working for the company. As we grew, I decided to hire a web developer to create a dispatching app (PWA). The application was my first experience with professional software development and I became very excited to explore this space for myself. I eventually decided I no longer wanted to be in the moving industry and my only regret was not developing the software myself.